{
    "subject": "Saeed_Akhtar_Mirza",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Salim_Langde_Pe_Mat_Ro",
    "human_readable": "Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.899531900882721,
            "question": "Who directed the film Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8817404508590698,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.834320604801178,
            "question": "Who is Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7432272434234619,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.74122554063797,
            "question": "Is Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6846288442611694,
            "question": "What is the plot of Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6069468259811401,
            "question": "When was Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5670417547225952,
            "question": "Where was Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5469609498977661,
            "question": "What genre is the film Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.52455735206604,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro.",
            "html": "yago_14538_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_14538_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro filmed?",
            "html": "yago_14538_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro released?",
            "html": "yago_14538_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14538_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Saeed Akhtar Mirza is the director of the film \"Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}